{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548436175791","data":{"timestamp":" 1548436175790"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_200925"," gameId":" 740bb3f3-71fd-4e80-9040-464514819501"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548436176181","data":{"timestamp":" 1548436176181"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_200925"," gameId":" 740bb3f3-71fd-4e80-9040-464514819501"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548436176423","data":{"timestamp":" 1548436176422"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_200925"," gameId":" 740bb3f3-71fd-4e80-9040-464514819501"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548436176750","data":{"timestamp":" 1548436176749"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_200925"," gameId":" 740bb3f3-71fd-4e80-9040-464514819501"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548436176992","data":{"timestamp":" 1548436176991"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_200925"," gameId":" 740bb3f3-71fd-4e80-9040-464514819501"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548436180482","data":{"timestamp":" 1548436180481"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_200925"," gameId":" 740bb3f3-71fd-4e80-9040-464514819501"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hizi ni herufi kuu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HIZI"," userResponse":" HIZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548436180775","data":{"timestamp":" 1548436180775"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_200925"," gameId":" 740bb3f3-71fd-4e80-9040-464514819501"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hizi ni herufi kuu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548436181683","data":{"timestamp":" 1548436181683"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_200925"," gameId":" 740bb3f3-71fd-4e80-9040-464514819501"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hizi ni herufi kuu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HERUFI"," userResponse":" HERUFI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548436182114","data":{"timestamp":" 1548436182113"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_200925"," gameId":" 740bb3f3-71fd-4e80-9040-464514819501"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hizi ni herufi kuu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUU"," userResponse":" KUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548436185111","data":{"timestamp":" 1548436185110"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_200925"," gameId":" 740bb3f3-71fd-4e80-9040-464514819501"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAMKA"," userResponse":" TAMKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548436185399","data":{"timestamp":" 1548436185398"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_200925"," gameId":" 740bb3f3-71fd-4e80-9040-464514819501"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548436186251","data":{"timestamp":" 1548436186250"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_200925"," gameId":" 740bb3f3-71fd-4e80-9040-464514819501"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAUTI"," userResponse":" SAUTI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548436186926","data":{"timestamp":" 1548436186925"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_200925"," gameId":" 740bb3f3-71fd-4e80-9040-464514819501"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUU"," userResponse":" KUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548436187670","data":{"timestamp":" 1548436187670"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_200925"," gameId":" 740bb3f3-71fd-4e80-9040-464514819501"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548436188003","data":{"timestamp":" 1548436188002"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_200925"," gameId":" 740bb3f3-71fd-4e80-9040-464514819501"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548436188296","data":{"timestamp":" 1548436188295"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_200925"," gameId":" 740bb3f3-71fd-4e80-9040-464514819501"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548436188616","data":{"timestamp":" 1548436188615"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_200925"," gameId":" 740bb3f3-71fd-4e80-9040-464514819501"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548436188902","data":{"timestamp":" 1548436188901"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_200925"," gameId":" 740bb3f3-71fd-4e80-9040-464514819501"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548436192629","data":{"timestamp":" 1548436192628"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_200925"," gameId":" 740bb3f3-71fd-4e80-9040-464514819501"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548436193023","data":{"timestamp":" 1548436193023"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_200925"," gameId":" 740bb3f3-71fd-4e80-9040-464514819501"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548436193265","data":{"timestamp":" 1548436193265"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_200925"," gameId":" 740bb3f3-71fd-4e80-9040-464514819501"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548436193587","data":{"timestamp":" 1548436193587"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_200925"," gameId":" 740bb3f3-71fd-4e80-9040-464514819501"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548436193828","data":{"timestamp":" 1548436193828"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_200925"," gameId":" 740bb3f3-71fd-4e80-9040-464514819501"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548436197306","data":{"timestamp":" 1548436197306"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_200925"," gameId":" 740bb3f3-71fd-4e80-9040-464514819501"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hizi ni herufi kuu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HIZI"," userResponse":" HIZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548436197605","data":{"timestamp":" 1548436197605"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_200925"," gameId":" 740bb3f3-71fd-4e80-9040-464514819501"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hizi ni herufi kuu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548436198516","data":{"timestamp":" 1548436198516"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_200925"," gameId":" 740bb3f3-71fd-4e80-9040-464514819501"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hizi ni herufi kuu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HERUFI"," userResponse":" HERUFI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548436198951","data":{"timestamp":" 1548436198951"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_200925"," gameId":" 740bb3f3-71fd-4e80-9040-464514819501"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hizi ni herufi kuu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUU"," userResponse":" KUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548436201906","data":{"timestamp":" 1548436201906"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_200925"," gameId":" 740bb3f3-71fd-4e80-9040-464514819501"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAMKA"," userResponse":" TAMKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548436202195","data":{"timestamp":" 1548436202195"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_200925"," gameId":" 740bb3f3-71fd-4e80-9040-464514819501"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548436203047","data":{"timestamp":" 1548436203047"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_200925"," gameId":" 740bb3f3-71fd-4e80-9040-464514819501"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAUTI"," userResponse":" SAUTI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548436203723","data":{"timestamp":" 1548436203723"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_200925"," gameId":" 740bb3f3-71fd-4e80-9040-464514819501"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUU"," userResponse":" KUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548436204469","data":{"timestamp":" 1548436204468"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_200925"," gameId":" 740bb3f3-71fd-4e80-9040-464514819501"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548436204804","data":{"timestamp":" 1548436204803"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_200925"," gameId":" 740bb3f3-71fd-4e80-9040-464514819501"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548436205085","data":{"timestamp":" 1548436205084"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_200925"," gameId":" 740bb3f3-71fd-4e80-9040-464514819501"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548436205404","data":{"timestamp":" 1548436205404"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_200925"," gameId":" 740bb3f3-71fd-4e80-9040-464514819501"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548436205680","data":{"timestamp":" 1548436205679"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_200925"," gameId":" 740bb3f3-71fd-4e80-9040-464514819501"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548436209154","data":{"timestamp":" 1548436209153"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_200925"," gameId":" 740bb3f3-71fd-4e80-9040-464514819501"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548436209264","data":{"timestamp":" 1548436209263"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_200925"," gameId":" 740bb3f3-71fd-4e80-9040-464514819501"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.gen.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548436403716","data":{"timestamp":" 1548436403716"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_200925"," gameId":" 740bb3f3-71fd-4e80-9040-464514819501"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548436403789","data":{"timestamp":" 1548436403789"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_200925"," gameId":" 9c5016da-88c9-4eb0-93fa-f417cd67e1c6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.gen.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunajiuliza Kwa nini Yayeri ni mashuhuri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MASHUHURI"," userResponse":" MASHUHURI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.lc:vow.asc.A..Z.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548436410201","data":{"timestamp":" 1548436410200"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_200925"," gameId":" 9c5016da-88c9-4eb0-93fa-f417cd67e1c6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.gen.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Tunajiuliza Kwa nini Yayeri ni mashuhuri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"countingx:1_10__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548436415332","data":{"timestamp":" 1548436415332"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_200925"," gameId":" 3a57df3b-1628-4b91-8a94-f344fc2d5510"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" 0"," taskName":" Count to 10"," problemName":" 10"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" START"," userResponse":" START"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" tap"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"countingx:1_10__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548436427816","data":{"timestamp":" 1548436427815"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_200925"," gameId":" 3a57df3b-1628-4b91-8a94-f344fc2d5510"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" 0"," taskName":" Count to 10"," problemName":" 10"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" END"," userResponse":" END"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" tap"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"countingx:1_10__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548436430475","data":{"timestamp":" 1548436430475"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_200925"," gameId":" 3a57df3b-1628-4b91-8a94-f344fc2d5510"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" 0"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" 10"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548436430612","data":{"timestamp":" 1548436430612"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_200925"," gameId":" 3a57df3b-1628-4b91-8a94-f344fc2d5510"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" 0"," taskName":" Count to 10"," problemName":" 10"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" ENDPROBLEM"," userResponse":" ENDPROBLEM"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" ENDPROBLEM"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"countingx:1_10__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548436436964","data":{"timestamp":" 1548436436964"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_200925"," gameId":" 0f2329c8-ff9e-49b8-a6d3-258a74a4a0a5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" 0"," taskName":" Count to 10"," problemName":" 10"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" START"," userResponse":" START"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" tap"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"countingx:1_10__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548436457844","data":{"timestamp":" 1548436457844"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_200925"," gameId":" 0f2329c8-ff9e-49b8-a6d3-258a74a4a0a5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" 0"," taskName":" Count to 10"," problemName":" 10"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" END"," userResponse":" END"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" tap"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"countingx:1_10__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548436460884","data":{"timestamp":" 1548436460884"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_200925"," gameId":" 0f2329c8-ff9e-49b8-a6d3-258a74a4a0a5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" 0"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" 10"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548436460951","data":{"timestamp":" 1548436460950"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_200925"," gameId":" 0f2329c8-ff9e-49b8-a6d3-258a74a4a0a5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" 0"," taskName":" Count to 10"," problemName":" 10"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" ENDPROBLEM"," userResponse":" ENDPROBLEM"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" ENDPROBLEM"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"countingx:1_10__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548436467712","data":{"timestamp":" 1548436467711"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_200925"," gameId":" b18a8ee5-2413-4946-931b-1335edb0d9f6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" 0"," taskName":" Count to 10"," problemName":" 10"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" START"," userResponse":" START"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" tap"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"countingx:1_10__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548436480456","data":{"timestamp":" 1548436480456"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_200925"," gameId":" b18a8ee5-2413-4946-931b-1335edb0d9f6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" 0"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" 10"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548436480530","data":{"timestamp":" 1548436480530"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_200925"," gameId":" b18a8ee5-2413-4946-931b-1335edb0d9f6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" 0"," taskName":" Count to 10"," problemName":" 10"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" ENDPROBLEM"," userResponse":" ENDPROBLEM"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" ENDPROBLEM"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"countingx:1_10__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548436486871","data":{"timestamp":" 1548436486871"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_200925"," gameId":" 664acae1-c039-43a3-8e83-81ac21c79acb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" 0"," taskName":" Count to 10"," problemName":" 10"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" START"," userResponse":" START"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" tap"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"countingx:1_10__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548436505207","data":{"timestamp":" 1548436505207"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_200925"," gameId":" 664acae1-c039-43a3-8e83-81ac21c79acb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" 0"," taskName":" Count to 10"," problemName":" 10"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" END"," userResponse":" END"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" tap"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"countingx:1_10__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548436508169","data":{"timestamp":" 1548436508168"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_200925"," gameId":" 664acae1-c039-43a3-8e83-81ac21c79acb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" 0"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" 10"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548436508260","data":{"timestamp":" 1548436508260"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_200925"," gameId":" 664acae1-c039-43a3-8e83-81ac21c79acb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" 0"," taskName":" Count to 10"," problemName":" 10"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" ENDPROBLEM"," userResponse":" ENDPROBLEM"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" ENDPROBLEM"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.lc:vow.asc.A..Z.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548436515602","data":{"timestamp":" 1548436515602"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_200925"," gameId":" 664acae1-c039-43a3-8e83-81ac21c79acb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" 0"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" 10"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.lc:vow.asc.A..Z.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548436523566","data":{"timestamp":" 1548436523566"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_200925"," gameId":" 664acae1-c039-43a3-8e83-81ac21c79acb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" 0"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" 10"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.gen.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548436704318","data":{"timestamp":" 1548436704318"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_200925"," gameId":" 664acae1-c039-43a3-8e83-81ac21c79acb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" 0"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" 10"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548436704381","data":{"timestamp":" 1548436704381"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_200925"," gameId":" 891ee8da-455c-47c7-beab-f1db6da2dbe9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.gen.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hawakuingia ndani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDANI"," userResponse":" NDANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::vow.A..Z.asc.lc.6__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548436711019","data":{"timestamp":" 1548436711019"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_200925"," gameId":" 891ee8da-455c-47c7-beab-f1db6da2dbe9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.gen.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Hawakuingia ndani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL2.incr.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548436717648","data":{"timestamp":" 1548436717647"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_200925"," gameId":" 891ee8da-455c-47c7-beab-f1db6da2dbe9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.gen.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Hawakuingia ndani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.lc.dic:vow.asc.A..Z.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548436724509","data":{"timestamp":" 1548436724509"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_200925"," gameId":" 891ee8da-455c-47c7-beab-f1db6da2dbe9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.gen.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Hawakuingia ndani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548436729440","data":{"timestamp":" 1548436729440"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_200925"," gameId":" 891ee8da-455c-47c7-beab-f1db6da2dbe9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.gen.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Hawakuingia ndani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::vow.A..Z.asc.lc.6__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548436736602","data":{"timestamp":" 1548436736602"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_200925"," gameId":" 891ee8da-455c-47c7-beab-f1db6da2dbe9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.gen.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Hawakuingia ndani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL2.incr.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548436746549","data":{"timestamp":" 1548436746549"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_200925"," gameId":" fcf29639-5cac-4b1c-b8ce-fbc59df5c593"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL2.incr.3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_9_9-11-7"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 9"," userResponse":" 11"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL2.incr.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548436753118","data":{"timestamp":" 1548436753118"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_200925"," gameId":" fcf29639-5cac-4b1c-b8ce-fbc59df5c593"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL2.incr.3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_9_9-11-7"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.lc.dic:vow.asc.A..Z.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548436760558","data":{"timestamp":" 1548436760557"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_200925"," gameId":" fcf29639-5cac-4b1c-b8ce-fbc59df5c593"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL2.incr.3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_9_9-11-7"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548436768232","data":{"timestamp":" 1548436768231"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_200925"," gameId":" fcf29639-5cac-4b1c-b8ce-fbc59df5c593"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL2.incr.3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_9_9-11-7"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::vow.A..Z.asc.lc.6__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548436775394","data":{"timestamp":" 1548436775394"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_200925"," gameId":" fcf29639-5cac-4b1c-b8ce-fbc59df5c593"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL2.incr.3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_9_9-11-7"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"num.scale:2..12.off1.2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548436801036","data":{"timestamp":" 1548436801036"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_200925"," gameId":" fcf29639-5cac-4b1c-b8ce-fbc59df5c593"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL2.incr.3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_9_9-11-7"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"num.scale:2..12.off1.2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548436846218","data":{"timestamp":" 1548436846217"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_200925"," gameId":" fcf29639-5cac-4b1c-b8ce-fbc59df5c593"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL2.incr.3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_9_9-11-7"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.lc.dic:vow.asc.A..Z.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548436865211","data":{"timestamp":" 1548436865211"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_200925"," gameId":" 47227db7-d7b4-4be7-86d2-6bd09c9c73c3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.lc.dic_vow.asc.A..Z.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_g"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" g"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.lc.dic:vow.asc.A..Z.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548436879056","data":{"timestamp":" 1548436879056"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_200925"," gameId":" 47227db7-d7b4-4be7-86d2-6bd09c9c73c3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.lc.dic_vow.asc.A..Z.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_a"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" 9"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 5"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.lc.dic:vow.asc.A..Z.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548436887923","data":{"timestamp":" 1548436887923"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_200925"," gameId":" 47227db7-d7b4-4be7-86d2-6bd09c9c73c3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.lc.dic_vow.asc.A..Z.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_a"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" 9"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 5"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.lc.dic:vow.asc.A..Z.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548436891327","data":{"timestamp":" 1548436891327"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_200925"," gameId":" 47227db7-d7b4-4be7-86d2-6bd09c9c73c3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.lc.dic_vow.asc.A..Z.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_a"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" <space>"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 5"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.lc.dic:vow.asc.A..Z.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548436900143","data":{"timestamp":" 1548436900143"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_200925"," gameId":" 47227db7-d7b4-4be7-86d2-6bd09c9c73c3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.lc.dic_vow.asc.A..Z.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_a"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" o"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 5"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.lc.dic:vow.asc.A..Z.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548436909930","data":{"timestamp":" 1548436909930"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_200925"," gameId":" 47227db7-d7b4-4be7-86d2-6bd09c9c73c3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.lc.dic_vow.asc.A..Z.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_a"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" g"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 5"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.lc.dic:vow.asc.A..Z.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548436920644","data":{"timestamp":" 1548436920644"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_200925"," gameId":" 47227db7-d7b4-4be7-86d2-6bd09c9c73c3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.lc.dic_vow.asc.A..Z.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_a"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" o"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 5"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.lc.dic:vow.asc.A..Z.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548436923082","data":{"timestamp":" 1548436923081"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_200925"," gameId":" 47227db7-d7b4-4be7-86d2-6bd09c9c73c3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.lc.dic_vow.asc.A..Z.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write_a"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548436970859","data":{"timestamp":" 1548436970859"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_200925"," gameId":" 47227db7-d7b4-4be7-86d2-6bd09c9c73c3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.lc.dic_vow.asc.A..Z.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write_a"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.lc.dic:vow.asc.A..Z.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548436978806","data":{"timestamp":" 1548436978806"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_200925"," gameId":" 47227db7-d7b4-4be7-86d2-6bd09c9c73c3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.lc.dic_vow.asc.A..Z.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write_a"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548436991783","data":{"timestamp":" 1548436991781"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_200925"," gameId":" 61a143d3-0e77-426b-80a9-d3a330b04f00"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_10_10-2-4"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 10"," userResponse":" 4"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548436999051","data":{"timestamp":" 1548436999050"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_200925"," gameId":" 61a143d3-0e77-426b-80a9-d3a330b04f00"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_10_10-2-4"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:vow.ltr.lc:A..Z.vow.5.asc.say.12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548437006081","data":{"timestamp":" 1548437006081"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_200925"," gameId":" 61a143d3-0e77-426b-80a9-d3a330b04f00"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_10_10-2-4"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548437015546","data":{"timestamp":" 1548437015546"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_200925"," gameId":" 61a143d3-0e77-426b-80a9-d3a330b04f00"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_10_10-2-4"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548437022598","data":{"timestamp":" 1548437022598"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_200925"," gameId":" 61a143d3-0e77-426b-80a9-d3a330b04f00"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_10_10-2-4"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"num.scale:2..12.off1.2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548437069640","data":{"timestamp":" 1548437069640"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_200925"," gameId":" 61a143d3-0e77-426b-80a9-d3a330b04f00"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_10_10-2-4"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-A.rand.16__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548437100539","data":{"timestamp":" 1548437100539"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_200925"," gameId":" c04ba7fb-f9c9-462e-85d8-1a89d31d6f7e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.16__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ALICHEZA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALICHEZA"," userResponse":" ALICHEZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-A.rand.16__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548437106306","data":{"timestamp":" 1548437106306"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_200925"," gameId":" c04ba7fb-f9c9-462e-85d8-1a89d31d6f7e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.16__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" ALICHEZA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548437106595","data":{"timestamp":" 1548437106595"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_200925"," gameId":" c04ba7fb-f9c9-462e-85d8-1a89d31d6f7e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.16__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ALICHEZA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALICHEZA"," userResponse":" ALICHEZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548437154248","data":{"timestamp":" 1548437154248"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_200925"," gameId":" 951c2a86-4289-48fd-9296-3350b570d4ce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" maua_maua-chuma-simu-vyema"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" maua"," userResponse":" vyema"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548437159358","data":{"timestamp":" 1548437159358"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_200925"," gameId":" 951c2a86-4289-48fd-9296-3350b570d4ce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" maua_maua-chuma-simu-vyema"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" maua"," userResponse":" simu"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548437163931","data":{"timestamp":" 1548437163930"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_200925"," gameId":" 951c2a86-4289-48fd-9296-3350b570d4ce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" maua_maua-chuma-simu-vyema"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" maua"," userResponse":" chuma"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548437167306","data":{"timestamp":" 1548437167305"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_200925"," gameId":" 951c2a86-4289-48fd-9296-3350b570d4ce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" maua_maua-chuma-simu-vyema"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" maua"," userResponse":" maua"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548437210395","data":{"timestamp":" 1548437210395"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_200925"," gameId":" 951c2a86-4289-48fd-9296-3350b570d4ce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mbaazi_mafuta-mbaazi-kaka-dukani"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" mbaazi"," userResponse":" dukani"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548437217147","data":{"timestamp":" 1548437217147"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_200925"," gameId":" 951c2a86-4289-48fd-9296-3350b570d4ce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mbaazi_mafuta-mbaazi-kaka-dukani"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" mbaazi"," userResponse":" mafuta"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548437220821","data":{"timestamp":" 1548437220821"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_200925"," gameId":" 951c2a86-4289-48fd-9296-3350b570d4ce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mbaazi_mafuta-mbaazi-kaka-dukani"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" mbaazi"," userResponse":" mbaazi"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548437253118","data":{"timestamp":" 1548437253118"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_200925"," gameId":" 951c2a86-4289-48fd-9296-3350b570d4ce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" mbaazi_mafuta-mbaazi-kaka-dukani"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548437253274","data":{"timestamp":" 1548437253274"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_200925"," gameId":" 951c2a86-4289-48fd-9296-3350b570d4ce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipanda bustani kubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUBWA"," userResponse":" KUBWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..A.all.rand.all.stat.show.27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548437263939","data":{"timestamp":" 1548437263939"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_200925"," gameId":" c8b48e0c-5099-4253-80c5-274dadc2515d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..A.all.rand.all.stat.show.27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_A_R-A-H"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..A.all.rand.all.stat.show.27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548437270836","data":{"timestamp":" 1548437270836"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_200925"," gameId":" c8b48e0c-5099-4253-80c5-274dadc2515d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..A.all.rand.all.stat.show.27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_A_V-A-L"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..A.all.rand.all.stat.show.27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548437274829","data":{"timestamp":" 1548437274829"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_200925"," gameId":" c8b48e0c-5099-4253-80c5-274dadc2515d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..A.all.rand.all.stat.show.27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_A_U-L-A"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..A.all.rand.all.stat.show.27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548437279227","data":{"timestamp":" 1548437279227"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_200925"," gameId":" c8b48e0c-5099-4253-80c5-274dadc2515d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..A.all.rand.all.stat.show.27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_A_A-R-N"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..A.all.rand.all.stat.show.27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548437282941","data":{"timestamp":" 1548437282941"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_200925"," gameId":" c8b48e0c-5099-4253-80c5-274dadc2515d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..A.all.rand.all.stat.show.27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_A_A-W-J"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..A.all.rand.all.stat.show.27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548437286708","data":{"timestamp":" 1548437286708"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_200925"," gameId":" c8b48e0c-5099-4253-80c5-274dadc2515d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..A.all.rand.all.stat.show.27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_A_W-E-A"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..A.all.rand.all.stat.show.27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548437289994","data":{"timestamp":" 1548437289994"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_200925"," gameId":" c8b48e0c-5099-4253-80c5-274dadc2515d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..A.all.rand.all.stat.show.27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_A_A-S-E"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..A.all.rand.all.stat.show.27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548437293561","data":{"timestamp":" 1548437293561"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_200925"," gameId":" c8b48e0c-5099-4253-80c5-274dadc2515d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..A.all.rand.all.stat.show.27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_A_J-A-T"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..A.all.rand.all.stat.show.27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548437297187","data":{"timestamp":" 1548437297187"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_200925"," gameId":" c8b48e0c-5099-4253-80c5-274dadc2515d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..A.all.rand.all.stat.show.27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_A_L-A-CH"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..A.all.rand.all.stat.show.27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548437300824","data":{"timestamp":" 1548437300824"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_200925"," gameId":" c8b48e0c-5099-4253-80c5-274dadc2515d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..A.all.rand.all.stat.show.27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_A_A-Y-I"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..A.all.rand.all.stat.show.27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548437306575","data":{"timestamp":" 1548437306574"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_200925"," gameId":" c8b48e0c-5099-4253-80c5-274dadc2515d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..A.all.rand.all.stat.show.27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_A_A-Y-I"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548437327985","data":{"timestamp":" 1548437327985"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_200925"," gameId":" 0ad66fc3-4bed-432f-bd3f-e44cf18e6ed2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_3_8-3-5"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 3"," userResponse":" 3"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548437333473","data":{"timestamp":" 1548437333473"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_200925"," gameId":" 0ad66fc3-4bed-432f-bd3f-e44cf18e6ed2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_9_9-2-7"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 9"," userResponse":" 2"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548437343497","data":{"timestamp":" 1548437343497"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_200925"," gameId":" 0ad66fc3-4bed-432f-bd3f-e44cf18e6ed2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_9_9-2-7"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 9"," userResponse":" 9"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548437353688","data":{"timestamp":" 1548437353688"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_200925"," gameId":" 0ad66fc3-4bed-432f-bd3f-e44cf18e6ed2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_10_10-2-4"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 10"," userResponse":" 4"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548437362633","data":{"timestamp":" 1548437362633"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_200925"," gameId":" 0ad66fc3-4bed-432f-bd3f-e44cf18e6ed2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_10_10-2-4"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 10"," userResponse":" 2"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548437371631","data":{"timestamp":" 1548437371631"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_200925"," gameId":" 0ad66fc3-4bed-432f-bd3f-e44cf18e6ed2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_10_10-2-4"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 10"," userResponse":" 10"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548437380510","data":{"timestamp":" 1548437380510"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_200925"," gameId":" 0ad66fc3-4bed-432f-bd3f-e44cf18e6ed2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_7_3-4-7"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 7"," userResponse":" 3"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548437389092","data":{"timestamp":" 1548437389091"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_200925"," gameId":" 0ad66fc3-4bed-432f-bd3f-e44cf18e6ed2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_7_3-4-7"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..A.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.28","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548437400545","data":{"timestamp":" 1548437400544"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_200925"," gameId":" 0ad66fc3-4bed-432f-bd3f-e44cf18e6ed2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_7_3-4-7"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548437411717","data":{"timestamp":" 1548437411717"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_200925"," gameId":" 0ad66fc3-4bed-432f-bd3f-e44cf18e6ed2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_7_3-4-7"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548437427055","data":{"timestamp":" 1548437427055"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_200925"," gameId":" fd6fde1a-c107-4009-ba2b-9fc0ede99d95"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A B CH D E F G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548437427438","data":{"timestamp":" 1548437427438"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_200925"," gameId":" fd6fde1a-c107-4009-ba2b-9fc0ede99d95"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A B CH D E F G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548437427926","data":{"timestamp":" 1548437427925"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_200925"," gameId":" fd6fde1a-c107-4009-ba2b-9fc0ede99d95"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A B CH D E F G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548437428280","data":{"timestamp":" 1548437428277"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_200925"," gameId":" fd6fde1a-c107-4009-ba2b-9fc0ede99d95"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A B CH D E F G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548437428691","data":{"timestamp":" 1548437428691"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_200925"," gameId":" fd6fde1a-c107-4009-ba2b-9fc0ede99d95"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A B CH D E F G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548437429177","data":{"timestamp":" 1548437429177"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_200925"," gameId":" fd6fde1a-c107-4009-ba2b-9fc0ede99d95"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A B CH D E F G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548437429403","data":{"timestamp":" 1548437429402"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_200925"," gameId":" fd6fde1a-c107-4009-ba2b-9fc0ede99d95"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A B CH D E F G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548437432573","data":{"timestamp":" 1548437432573"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_200925"," gameId":" fd6fde1a-c107-4009-ba2b-9fc0ede99d95"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548437432610","data":{"timestamp":" 1548437432609"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_200925"," gameId":" fd6fde1a-c107-4009-ba2b-9fc0ede99d95"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548437433326","data":{"timestamp":" 1548437433326"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_200925"," gameId":" fd6fde1a-c107-4009-ba2b-9fc0ede99d95"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" J"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548437433723","data":{"timestamp":" 1548437433723"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_200925"," gameId":" fd6fde1a-c107-4009-ba2b-9fc0ede99d95"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" K"," userResponse":" K"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548437434018","data":{"timestamp":" 1548437434018"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_200925"," gameId":" fd6fde1a-c107-4009-ba2b-9fc0ede99d95"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" L"," userResponse":" L"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548437434245","data":{"timestamp":" 1548437434245"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_200925"," gameId":" fd6fde1a-c107-4009-ba2b-9fc0ede99d95"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" M"," userResponse":" M"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548437434452","data":{"timestamp":" 1548437434452"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_200925"," gameId":" fd6fde1a-c107-4009-ba2b-9fc0ede99d95"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" N"," userResponse":" N"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548437434776","data":{"timestamp":" 1548437434776"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_200925"," gameId":" fd6fde1a-c107-4009-ba2b-9fc0ede99d95"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548437435000","data":{"timestamp":" 1548437435000"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_200925"," gameId":" fd6fde1a-c107-4009-ba2b-9fc0ede99d95"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548437438156","data":{"timestamp":" 1548437438156"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_200925"," gameId":" fd6fde1a-c107-4009-ba2b-9fc0ede99d95"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" R S"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" R"," userResponse":" R"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548437438568","data":{"timestamp":" 1548437438567"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_200925"," gameId":" fd6fde1a-c107-4009-ba2b-9fc0ede99d95"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" R S"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" S"," userResponse":" S"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548437441102","data":{"timestamp":" 1548437441102"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_200925"," gameId":" fd6fde1a-c107-4009-ba2b-9fc0ede99d95"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" T U V"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" T"," userResponse":" T"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548437441317","data":{"timestamp":" 1548437441317"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_200925"," gameId":" fd6fde1a-c107-4009-ba2b-9fc0ede99d95"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" T U V"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548437441522","data":{"timestamp":" 1548437441521"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_200925"," gameId":" fd6fde1a-c107-4009-ba2b-9fc0ede99d95"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" T U V"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" V"," userResponse":" V"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548437444981","data":{"timestamp":" 1548437444981"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_200925"," gameId":" fd6fde1a-c107-4009-ba2b-9fc0ede99d95"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" W"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" W"," userResponse":" W"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548437448810","data":{"timestamp":" 1548437448810"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_200925"," gameId":" fd6fde1a-c107-4009-ba2b-9fc0ede99d95"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Y Z"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Y"," userResponse":" Y"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548437449835","data":{"timestamp":" 1548437449834"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_200925"," gameId":" fd6fde1a-c107-4009-ba2b-9fc0ede99d95"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Y Z"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Z"," userResponse":" Z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548437452525","data":{"timestamp":" 1548437452525"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_200925"," gameId":" fd6fde1a-c107-4009-ba2b-9fc0ede99d95"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A B CH D E F G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548437452899","data":{"timestamp":" 1548437452899"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_200925"," gameId":" fd6fde1a-c107-4009-ba2b-9fc0ede99d95"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A B CH D E F G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548437453398","data":{"timestamp":" 1548437453398"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_200925"," gameId":" fd6fde1a-c107-4009-ba2b-9fc0ede99d95"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A B CH D E F G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548437453766","data":{"timestamp":" 1548437453766"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_200925"," gameId":" fd6fde1a-c107-4009-ba2b-9fc0ede99d95"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A B CH D E F G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548437454185","data":{"timestamp":" 1548437454184"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_200925"," gameId":" fd6fde1a-c107-4009-ba2b-9fc0ede99d95"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A B CH D E F G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548437454668","data":{"timestamp":" 1548437454668"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_200925"," gameId":" fd6fde1a-c107-4009-ba2b-9fc0ede99d95"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A B CH D E F G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548437454895","data":{"timestamp":" 1548437454894"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_200925"," gameId":" fd6fde1a-c107-4009-ba2b-9fc0ede99d95"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A B CH D E F G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548437465596","data":{"timestamp":" 1548437465596"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_200925"," gameId":" fd6fde1a-c107-4009-ba2b-9fc0ede99d95"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548437465640","data":{"timestamp":" 1548437465640"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_200925"," gameId":" fd6fde1a-c107-4009-ba2b-9fc0ede99d95"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548437466354","data":{"timestamp":" 1548437466354"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_200925"," gameId":" fd6fde1a-c107-4009-ba2b-9fc0ede99d95"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" J"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548437466748","data":{"timestamp":" 1548437466748"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_200925"," gameId":" fd6fde1a-c107-4009-ba2b-9fc0ede99d95"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" K"," userResponse":" K"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548437467045","data":{"timestamp":" 1548437467045"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_200925"," gameId":" fd6fde1a-c107-4009-ba2b-9fc0ede99d95"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" L"," userResponse":" L"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548437467251","data":{"timestamp":" 1548437467251"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_200925"," gameId":" fd6fde1a-c107-4009-ba2b-9fc0ede99d95"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" M"," userResponse":" M"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548437467447","data":{"timestamp":" 1548437467447"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_200925"," gameId":" fd6fde1a-c107-4009-ba2b-9fc0ede99d95"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" N"," userResponse":" N"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548437467763","data":{"timestamp":" 1548437467763"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_200925"," gameId":" fd6fde1a-c107-4009-ba2b-9fc0ede99d95"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548437467988","data":{"timestamp":" 1548437467988"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_200925"," gameId":" fd6fde1a-c107-4009-ba2b-9fc0ede99d95"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548437470699","data":{"timestamp":" 1548437470698"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_200925"," gameId":" fd6fde1a-c107-4009-ba2b-9fc0ede99d95"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548437470851","data":{"timestamp":" 1548437470851"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_200925"," gameId":" fd6fde1a-c107-4009-ba2b-9fc0ede99d95"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548437482531","data":{"timestamp":" 1548437482531"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_200925"," gameId":" 32c071d4-891a-4338-b732-9d68c4284a53"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_10_10-2-4"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 10"," userResponse":" 10"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548437485996","data":{"timestamp":" 1548437485995"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_200925"," gameId":" 32c071d4-891a-4338-b732-9d68c4284a53"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_10_10-2-4"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..A.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.28","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548437502182","data":{"timestamp":" 1548437502181"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_200925"," gameId":" 32c071d4-891a-4338-b732-9d68c4284a53"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_10_10-2-4"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..A.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.28","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548437523946","data":{"timestamp":" 1548437523946"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_200925"," gameId":" ff368002-2bb4-40e5-b80c-cbaa3fd4026a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..A.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.28"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_A_A-N-T"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..A.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.28","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548437528947","data":{"timestamp":" 1548437528947"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_200925"," gameId":" ff368002-2bb4-40e5-b80c-cbaa3fd4026a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..A.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.28"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_A_F-A-U"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..A.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.28","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548437533616","data":{"timestamp":" 1548437533616"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_200925"," gameId":" ff368002-2bb4-40e5-b80c-cbaa3fd4026a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..A.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.28"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_A_B-K-A"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..A.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.28","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548437537738","data":{"timestamp":" 1548437537737"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_200925"," gameId":" ff368002-2bb4-40e5-b80c-cbaa3fd4026a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..A.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.28"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_A_Y-M-A"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..A.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.28","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548437541683","data":{"timestamp":" 1548437541683"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_200925"," gameId":" ff368002-2bb4-40e5-b80c-cbaa3fd4026a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..A.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.28"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_A_U-A-N"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..A.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.28","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548437545828","data":{"timestamp":" 1548437545827"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_200925"," gameId":" ff368002-2bb4-40e5-b80c-cbaa3fd4026a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..A.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.28"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_A_A-M-B"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..A.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.28","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548437552756","data":{"timestamp":" 1548437552756"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_200925"," gameId":" ff368002-2bb4-40e5-b80c-cbaa3fd4026a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..A.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.28"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_A_A-H-E"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..A.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.28","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548437556590","data":{"timestamp":" 1548437556590"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_200925"," gameId":" ff368002-2bb4-40e5-b80c-cbaa3fd4026a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..A.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.28"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_A_A-B-CH"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..A.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.28","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548437561321","data":{"timestamp":" 1548437561321"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_200925"," gameId":" ff368002-2bb4-40e5-b80c-cbaa3fd4026a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..A.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.28"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_A_R-A-F"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..A.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.28","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548437565064","data":{"timestamp":" 1548437565064"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_200925"," gameId":" ff368002-2bb4-40e5-b80c-cbaa3fd4026a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..A.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.28"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_A_J-A-H"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..A.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.28","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548437570900","data":{"timestamp":" 1548437570899"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_200925"," gameId":" ff368002-2bb4-40e5-b80c-cbaa3fd4026a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..A.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.28"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_A_J-A-H"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548437634059","data":{"timestamp":" 1548437634059"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_200925"," gameId":" c251c7d5-de6a-4649-9980-dd165cf866fd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" huo_ndege-huyo-pale-huo"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" huo"," userResponse":" huo"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"end":"end"}]}